Guide to the Veterinary Reprint and Pamphlet Collection, 1865-1950
Veterinary Reprint and Pamphlet Collection, 1865-1950
- H
  - ________. "The pathogenicity of the saprophytic acid-fast bacilli." Reprinted from Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, Vol.LXXXI, N.S.34, No.6, December 1932. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Six years' experience with a herd experimentally infected with Johne's disease." Reprinted from Cornell Veterinarian, Vol.XXIII, No.1, January 1933. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The State Veterinary College, the veterinary profession, and the livestock owner." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, Vol.XXV, No.3, July 1935. (Box 2)
  - ________ and Alexander Zeissig. "Studies on the control of Johne's disease." Reprinted from the Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, Vol.LXXXII, N.S.35, No.3, March 1933. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Studies on the disease of guinea pigs due to bacillus abortus." Reprinted from the Journal of Experimental Medicine, December 1922. (Box 2)
  - ________ and J. Traum. "Studies in intradermal tuberculin." Reprinted from Cornell Veterinarian, April 1924. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Subcutaneous lesions which sometimes induce tuberculin hypersensitiveness in cattle." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, Vol.XIX, No.2, April 1929. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Subcutaneous lesions which sometimes induce tuberculin hypersensitiveness in cattle." Reprinted from the Annual Report of the New York State Veterinary College, 1928-1929. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The susceptibility of mice and rats to infection with bacillus abortus." Reprinted from The Journal of Experimental Medicine, December 1922. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The value of heat-killed cultures for the prevention of the bacillus abortus inoculation disease of guinea pigs." Reprinted from The Journal of Experimental Medicine, December 1922. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The value of placental examination for the diagnosis of infectious abortion of cattle." Reprinted from the 1926 Annual Report of the State Veterinary College. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The veterinarian's contribution to human welfare." Seventy-fifth Anniversary Kansas State College Bulletin, Vol.XXII, No.10, November 1938. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Veterinary education in the postwar world." Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, Vol.CIII, No.800, November 1943. (Box 2)
  - ________. "What about the future of veterinary practice?" The Cornell Veterinarian, Vol.XXXI, No.2, April 1941. (Box 2)
  - Haden, Russell, L. "Blood chemistry and the gastrointestinal tract." Reprinted from The Journal of Laboratory and Clinical Medicine, May 1931. (Box 2)
  - Hadwen, Seymour and E.A. Bruce. "Observations on the migration of warble larvae through the tissues." Department of Agriculture, Canada, Health of Animals Branch, Scientific Series, Bulletin No.22, 1916. (Box 2)
  - Hadwen, Seymour. "Warble flies: the economic aspect and a contribution on the biology." Department of Agriculture, Canada, Health of Animals Branch, Bulletin No.16, November 1912. (Box 2)
  - Hardenbergh, J.B. and Fred Boerner Jr. "Vaccinations against hemorrhagic septicemia, no. 2." Reprinted from The Journal of American Veterinary Medicine, March 1917. (Box 2)
  - Harding, H.A. "Effect of temperature of pasteurization on the creaming ability of milk." University of Illinois Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 237, December 1921. (Box 2)
  - _________, Geo. A. Smith and V.A. Moore. "A healthy herd from a tuberculous herd." New York Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 77, April 1906. (Box 2)
  - _________and L.L Van Slyke. "Chloroform as an aid in the study of milk enzymes." New York Agricultural Experiment Station, Technical Bulletin No. 6, December 1907. (Box 2)
  - ________and J.K. Wilson. "A study of the udder flora of cows." Technical Bulletin No. 27, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Haring, C.M., W.A. Sawyer and D.N. Morgan. "Bovine tuberculosis investigations." Reprinted from the Proceedings of the Forty-sixth Annual Convention of the American Veterinary Medical Association, 1909. (Box 2)
  - Haring, C.M. and Ralph M. Bell. "The intradermal test for tuberculosis in cattle and hogs." College of Agriculture Agricultural Experiment Station, Berkeley, California, Bulletin No. 23, March 1914. (Box 2)
  - Hassall, Albert and C.W. Stiles. "Strongylus rubidus, a new species of nematode, parasitic in pigs." Reprinted from The Journal of Comparative Medicine and Veterinary Archives, April 1892. (Box 2)
  - Hasseltine, H.E. "Current studies of undulant fever." Reprinted from the Public Health Reports, 12 July 1929. (Box 2)
  - Hatcher, Robert A. "The work of the council on pharmacy and chemistry." Reprinted from The American Medical Asssociation Journal, 4 November 1916. (Box 2)
  - Hayden, C.E.. "The blood and urine of the cow in milk fever: a second report." Reprinted from the 1925 Annual Report of the State Veterinary College. (Box 2)
  - ________.and L.B. Sholl. "The blood and urine of the cow in milk fever." October 1925. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The blood sugar of the cow in milk fever." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, April 1927. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The constituents of the blood of animals as evidence of intestinal contribution to the cause of diseases of obscure origin." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian Vol. XX, No.2, April 1930. (Box 2)
  - ________ and Pierre A. Fish. "The normal blood of some domesticated animals." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, April 1928. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Orokinase and ptyalin in the saliva of the horse." Reprinted from The American Journal of Physiology, Vol. 45, No.4, March 1918. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The physiology of the blood of chickens." Reprinted from the Annual Report of the New York State Veterinary College at Cornell University for the year 1927-1928. (Box 2)
  - ________ and E.L. Brunett. "A study of the influence of bact. pullorum infection upon some organic and inorganic constituents of the blood of S.C. white leghorns." Annual Report of the State Veterinary College. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Sugar, Guanidine and cholesterol in the blood of the cow in milk fever." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian Vol. XIX, No.3, July 1929. (Box 2)
  - Heard, Dwight B. "Public grazing lands: the range homestead." Reprinted from The American Review of Reviews, September 1915. (Box 2)
  - Hendrickson, J.M. "Pokeweed berries not poisonous for chickens." Reprinted from the Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association, April 1931. (Box 2)
  - ________. and K.F. Hilbert. "The persistence of pasteurella avicida in the blood and organs of fowls with spontaneous fowl cholera." Reprinted from the Journal of Infectious Diseases, February, 1932, Vol.50. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Report of the poultry disease laboratory at Farmingdale, Long Island, July 1, 1927 to June 30, 1928." Reprinted from the Annual Report of the State Veterinary College at Cornell University, 1927-1928. (Box 2)
  - ________ and K.F. Hilbert. "Report of the poultry disease laboratory at Farmingdale, Long Island, July 1, 1928 to June 30, 1929." Annual Report of the State Veterinary College at Cornell University, 1928-1929. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Report of the poultry disease laboratory at Farmingdale, Long Island, July 1, 1929 to June 30, 1930." Annual Report of the State Veterinary College, Cornell University. (Box 2)
  - Henkel, Alice. "Wild Medicinal plants of the United States." U.S. Department of Agricuture Bureau of Plant Industry, Bulletin No. 89, 1906. (Box 2)
  - Hewitt, Charles N. "Infectious Diseases of hogs: a paper describing some of these diseases as they appear in swine." State Board of Health in Minnesota, 1894. (Box 2)
  - Hickman, Richard W. "Description and treatment of scabies in cattle." U.S. Department of Agriculture Bureau of Animal Industry, Bulletin No. 40, 1902. (Box 2)
  - Higgins, Chas. H. "Actinobacillosis." Department of Agriculture, Canada, Health of Animals Branch, Biological Laboratory, Bulletin No.1, March 1904. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Entero-hepatitis, or black-head in turkeys." Department of Agriculture, Canada, Health of Animals Branch, Bulletin No.17, February 1915. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Entero-hepatitis or black-head and the biological laboratory system of raising turkeys." Department of Agriculture, Canada, Health of Animals Branch, Bulletin No.19, January 1916. (Box 2)
  - Hill, R.L. "The physical curd character of milk and its relationship to the digestibility of food value of milk for infants." Utah Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 207, June 1928. (Box 2)
  - Hilton, William A. "The morphology and development of intestinal folds and villi in vertebrates." Reprinted form The American Journal of Anatomy, 15 September 1902. (Box 2)
  - Hoard, W.D. "Responsibility of the veterinarian to the dairyman [delivered at the New York State Veterinary College, 15 December 1909]." 1909. (Box 2)
  - Hoffman. "Treatment of tuberculosis by means of glandulen: a specific organic remedy." ca. 1899. (Box 2)
  - Holden, Edgar and John Gray. "Adamantinoma of the tibia." Journal of Bone and Joint Surgery, April 1934. (Box 2)
  - Holmes, Edmund W. "The defects of our present methods of teaching anatomy in our medical schools." Reprinted from Proceedings of the Association of American Anatomists, 28-30 December 1898. (Box 2)
  - Hopkins, Grant Sherman. "[Address by Grant Sherman Hopkins]." Reprinted from the Cornell Veterinarian, Vol.XXIV, No.2, April 1934. (Box 2)
  - __________. "Apparatus for illustrating the circulation of the lymph." Reprinted from Proceedings of the American Micropathology Sociey, 1895. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The correlation of anatomy and epidural anaesthesia in domestic animals." Reprinted from the Annual Report of the New York State Veterinary College at Cornell University for the year 1934-1935. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The heart of some lungless salamanders." Reprinted from the American Naturalist, October 1896. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The innervation of the muscle retractor oculi." Reprinted from The Anatomical Record, Vol.11, No.5, December 1916. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The lymphatics and enteric epithelium of amia calva." Reprinted from the Wilder Quarter-Century Book, 1893. (Box 2)
  - ________. "On the enteron of American ganoids." Reprinted from Journal of Morphology, 1895. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Structure of the stomach of amia calva." Reprinted from the Proceedings of the American Society of Microscopists, Thirteenth Annual Meeting, 1890. (Box 2)
  - Howard, George E. "Standard varieties of chickens." U.S. Department of Agriculture Farmers' Bulletin, No. 51, 1897. (Box 2)
  - Howe, William A. "Mutual helpfulness in the conservation of public health." Read before the New York State Medical Society, 19 April 1911. (Box 2)
  - Hubbard, Roger S. and Charles V. Noback. "Note on the concentration of the acetone bodies in normal blood and urine." Reprinted from The Journal of Biological Chemistry, Vol.LXIII, No.2, March 1925. (Box 2)
  - Huddleson, I. Forest. "A further epidemiological study of undulant fever in Michigan." Reprinted from Symposium on Undulant Fever, October 1928. (Box 2)
  - _________. "The differentiation of the species of the genus brucella." Reprinted from Symposium on Undulant Fever, October 1928. (Box 2)
  - __________. "The pathogenicity of the species of the genus brucella for monkeys." Reprinted from The Journal of Infectious Diseases, October 1929. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The differentiation of the species of the genus brucella." Agricultural Experiment Station, Michigan State College of Agriculture and Applied Science, Technical Bulletin, No. 100, August 1929. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The comparative pathogenicity of several strains of bacterium abortus (bang)." Agricultural Experiment Station, Michigan Agricultural College, Technical Bulletin, No. 55, March 1922. (Box 2)
  - ________. "Rapid macroscopic agglutination for the serum diagnosis of bang's abortion disease." Reprinted from The Journal of Infectious Diseases, March 1928. (Box 2)
  - Hughes, E.H. "The feeding value of raisins and dairy by-products for growing and fattening swine." University of California College of Agriculture Agricultural Experiment Station, Berkeley, California, Bulletin No. 440, November 1927. (Box 2)
- I
  - Iles, George. "Electricity uncovers a law of evolution." July 1909. (Box 2)
  - Iragorry, L. Briceño. "Contribución al estudio de las salmonelosis humanas en Venezuela." Reprinted from la Gaceta Médica de Caracas, Año LVI, Nos. 1-6, Enero-Marzo de 1948. (Box 2)
  - Istvan, Cselko. "A lefolozott tej mint takarmany kulonos tekintettel a suldohizlalasra." VIII. Nemzetkozi allatorvosi kongresszu Budapesten, 1905. (Box 2)
- J
  - Janos, Tatray. "Egyseges elvek megallapitasa a malleinreactio elbiralasara." VIII. Nemzetkozi allatorvosi kongresszu Budapesten, 1905. (Box 2)
  - Joest, E. "Bekampfung der schweineseuche und schweinepest; schutzimpfungen." VIII. Internationaler Tierarzlicher Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 2)
  - Johannsen, Oskar, A. "Tests of water by bacterial inoculaton." Reprinted from American Medicine, February 1907. (Box 2)
  - Jones, F.S. "Fatal Septicemia or bacillary white diarrhea in young chickens." Annual Report of the State Veterinary College, n.d. (Box 2)
  - __________. "An outbreak of an acute disease in adult fowls, due to bact pullorum." Journal of Medical Research, March 1913. (Box 2)
  - Jong, D.A. "Bekampfung der tuberkulose der Haustiere." VIII. Internationaler Tierarzlicher Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 2)
  - __________. "Rapports entre la tuberculose de l'homme, du gros betail, de la volaille, et d'autres animaus dometiques (notamment du chien)." VIII. Congres International de medecine veterinarie Budapest, 1905. (Box 2)
  - Jordan, David Star. "Observations on fur seals of the Pribilof Islands." A preliminary report, 1896. (Box 2)
  - Jordan, Edwin O. "The self-purification of streams." The Decennial Publications, 1903. (Box 2)
- K
  - Kanavel, Allen B. and Sumner L. Koch "The treatment of infected wounds on surgical service." Reprinted from Bulletin of the American College of Surgeons, 3 September 1930. (Box 2)
  - Kelser, R.A. and R.W. Mohri." Comparative germicidal tests of mercurochrome and tincture of iodine." Journal of the Amercian Veterinary Medical Association, January 1932. (Box 2)
  - King, Jesse L. "Localisation of the motor area in the sheep's brain by the histological method." Reprinted from The Journal of Comparative Neurology, Vol.21, No.3, June 1911. (Box 2)
  - King, Merrill J. and W.H. Park. "Effect of Calmett's BCG vaccine on experimental animals." American Journal of Public Health, February 1929. (Box 2)
  - Kingsbury, Benjamin F. "Atresia and the interstitial cells of the ovary." Reprinted from the American Journal of Anatomy, v.65, no.2, September 1939. (Box 2)
  - ________ and F.J. Roemer. "The development of the hypophysis of the dog." Reprinted from the American Journal of Anatomy, v.66, no.3, May 1940. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The development of the pharyngeal derivatives of the opossum (Didelphys virginiana), with special reference to the thymus." Reprinted from the American Journal of Anatomy, v.67, no.3, November 1940. (Box 2)
  - __________. "The encephalic evaginations in ganoids." Reprinted from The Journal of Comparative Neurology, April 1897. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The histoloical structures of the enteron of nectars maculatus." Reprinted from Proceedings of the American Microscopical Society, 1894. (Box 2)
  - ________. "On the fate of the ultimobranchial body within the human thyroid gland." Reprinted from the Anatomical Record, v.61, no.2, and supplement January 1935. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The postpartum formation of egg cells in the cat." Reprinted from the Journal of Morphology, v.63, no.2, September 1938. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The question of a lateral thyroid in mammals, with special reference to man." Reprinted from the American Journal of Anatomy, v.65, no.2, September 1939. (Box 2)
  - __________. "The spermatogenesis of desmognathus fusca." Reprinted from The American Journal of Anatomy, 28 February 1902. (Box 2)
  - __________. "The structure and morphology of the oblongata in fishes." Reprinted from The Journal of Comparative Neurology, April 1897. (Box 2)
  - ________. "The ultimobranchial body and thyroid gland in the fetal calf." Reprinted from the American Journal of Anatomy, v.56, no.3, May 15. (Box 2)
  - Kirby-Smith, J.L., W.E. Dove, and G.F. White. "Creeping Eruption." Reprinted from The Archives of Dermatology and Syphilogy, February 1926. (Box 2)
  - Kirkbride, Mary B. and Mary W. Wheeler. "Hemolytic streptococcus carriers: their relation to the spread of scarlet fever." Reprinted from The Journal of the American Medical Association, 22 October 1927. (Box 2)
  - Kjerrulf, Bericht von. "Verfalschung des fleisches und der fleischprodukte und die zu deren nachweise dieneden neueren untersuchungmethoden." VIII. Internationaler Tierarzlicher Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 2)
  - Klimmer, M. "Akute euterentzundungen." Elfter Internationaler Ierarztlicher Kingress, London, Auguest 1930. (Box 2)
  - Knodt, C.B. and G.W. Salisbury. "The effect of sulfanilamide upon the livability and metabolism of bovine spermatozoa." Reprinted from Journal of Diary Science, May 1946. (Box 2)
  - Kozlowski, Anthony. "Effect of ricinoleated vaccine of the hemolytic streptococcus (scarlet fever) on animals." Journal of Immunology, March1928. (Box 2)
- L
  - Lagerlof, Nils. "Nagra intryck fran en studieresa i nordamerika." 1930. (Box 3)
  - Laidlaw, Frank W. "Nuisances: Duties and Powers of Health Officers and Boards of Health." New York State Department of Health., n.d. (Box 3)
  - Lambert, James. "The germ theory of disease." A paper read before the Irish Central Veterinary Medical Society, 15 April 1883. (Box 3)
  - Landbrukshoiskole, Norges. "Avkastningskontrollen med svin." Reprinted from the Report of the Norwegian Agricultural School, 1934. (Box 3)
  - Lane, C.B. "The milking machine as a factor in dairying: a preliminary report." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Bulletin No. 92, 1907. (Box 3)
  - Langan, Enrique Martinez. "La inspeccion veterinaria municipal de la c. federal." Sociedad de Medicina Veterinaria, Buenes Aires, 1936. (Box 3)
  - Langworthy, C.F. "Fish as Food." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Farmers' Bulletin No. 85, 1898. (Box 3)
  - __________. "Eggs and their uses as food." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Farmers' Bulletin No. 128, 1901. (Box 3)
  - Law, James. "Bovine Tuberculosis." Reprinted from the Transactions of the Medical Society of the State of New York, 1900. (Box 3)
  - __________. "Importance of a Higher Veterinary Education: A Lecture Delieverd Before the State Agricultural Socity at Albany, 18 January 1893." (Box 3)
  - __________. "Transmission of Contagion by Immunization." American Journal of Veterinary Medicine, n.d. (Box 3)
  - __________. "Tuberculosis in relation to animal industry and public health." Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 65, April 1894. (Box 3)
  - __________. "Tuberculosis in Cattle and its Control." Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 150, July 1898 (Box 3)
  - Leclainche, M.E. "La Serotherapie des maladies infectieuses des animaux domestiqus." VIII. Congres International de medecine veterinaire a Budapest, 1905. (Box 3)
  - Lehnert, Edwin. "Autoisoantikörper als physiologische Substanzen im Pferdeblut." Reprinted from Skandinavisk Veterinärtidskrift för Bakteriologi, Patologi Etc., 1947. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Die Blutgruppen des Pferdes." Reprinted from Veterinarski archiv, Zagreb, knjiga XX/1950, svezak 10. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Ein weiterer Beitrag zur Frage der Existenz von Autoisoanikörpen im Pferdeblut." Reprinted from Nordisk Veterin Ærmedicin, Bd.1, 1949. (Box 3)
  - Lignieres, J. "les maladies tropicales des animaux domestiques." VIII. Congres International de medecine veterinaire a Budapest, 1905. (Box 3)
  - ________. "La serotherapie des maladies infectieuses chez les animaux domestiques." VIII. Congres International de medecine veterinaire a Budapest, 1905. (Box 3)
  - Lienaux, E. "Le cancer chez les animaux domestiques." VIII. Congres International de medecine veterinaire a Budapest, 1905. (Box 3)
  - Linch, Charles. "Contagious abortion. New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, Agricultural Bulletin, No 243, October 1930. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Private practitioners in tuberculosis eradication." Cornell Veterinarian, July 1923. (Box 3)
  - Linstow, Gottingen von. "Die durch tierische parasiten erzeugten tox ischen stoffe." VIII Congres International de Medecine Veterinaire, Budapest, 1905. (Box 3)
  - Loeffler, Bericht von. "Die Schutzimpfung gegen die maul-und klauenseuche." VIII Internationaler tierarzlicher congress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 3)
  - Logan, Walter S. "Laissez Faire." Address delivered before the post-graduate class of the Georgetown, D.C., Law School, 26 April 1902. (Box 3)
  - Logiudice, J.N. Gomi, and V. Pessacq. "La castracion de potrancas 'a campo.'"Reprinted from Revista de Medicina Veterinaria, May-June 1938. (Box 3)
  - Logiudice, J.N.and G.M. Aranes. "La anestesia por gases en los animales domesticos." Universidad Nacional de la Plata, 1946. (Box 3)
  - Lorenz, "Uber die art infection bei der tuberkulose der haustiere." VIII. Internationaler tierarzlicher congress in Budapest 1905. (Box 3)
  - Lucas, Frederic A. "Notes on the anatomy and affinities of the coerebidae and other American birds." Reprinted from Proceedings of the United States National Museum, 1894. (Box 3)
  - ________. "Notes on the preparation of rough skeletons." Part C of Buletin of the United States National Museum, 1891. (Box 3)
  - ________. "On the structure of the tongue in humming birds." Reprinted from Proceedings of the United States National Musuem, 1891. (Box 3)
  - Lucker, John T. "A new genus and new species of trematode worms of the family plagiorchiidaie." Reprinted from Proceedings of the United States National Musuem, 1931. (Box 3)
  - Lusk, Graham. "Fundamental Requirements of energy for proper nutrition." Reprinted from The Journal of American Medical Associations, 23 March 1918. (Box 3)
  - ______. "Pasteur, the man." Reprinted from Science, 2 February 1923. (Box 3)
  - Lydston, Frank G. "The Russianizing of Americnan Medicine and the Medical Dreyfus." From a meeting of the Mississippi Valley Medical Association, 10 November 1909. (Box 3)
- M
  - Mack, Winfred B. "The etiology and morbid anatomy of diptheria in chickens" Reprinted form the American Veterinary Review, January 1905. (Box 3)
  - __________and Edward Records. "The control of contagious epithelioma in chickens by vaccination." Agricultural Experiment Station the University of Nevada, Bulletin No. 82, June 1915. (Box 3)
  - MacDonald, Arthur. "Ethics as applied to criminology." Reprinted from The Journal of Mental Sciences, January 1891. (Box 3)
  - Malkmus, "Ausdehnung der Verkehrsbeschrankungen beim auftreten der nicht unmittelbar kontagosen infektionskrankheiten namentlich des milzbrandes." VIII. Internationaler Tierarzlicer Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 3)
  - Malm, Med. "Feststellung einheitlicher Grundsatze fer die beurteilung der tuberculin und mallein-reaktion." VIII. Internationaler Tierarzlicer Kongress in Budapest, 1905. (Box 3)
  - Manheimer, Wallace A. "The application of ozone to the purification of swimming pools." Reprinted from the United States Public Health Service Public Health Reports, 1918. (Box 3)
  - Martel, M.H. "Falsifications de la viande et des produits carnes alimentaires nouvaux moyens d'analyse." VIII. Congres International de medecine veterinarire a Budapest, 1905. (Box 3)
  - Mason, William. "Pure food legislation." A Speech before the Senate, 2 May 1900. (Box 3)